name: 'be: we, you, they, negatives'
questions:
  -
    question: '1. $ you from the United States?'
    answers:
      - is
      - are
      - am
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'No, we $ American. We’re English.'
    answers:
      - are
      - 'not are'
      - aren’t
    correct: 3
  -
    question: '$ they Spanish?'
    answers:
      - are
      - is
      - am
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'They $ from Madrid.'
    answers:
      - is
      - am
      - are
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'Nikolai $ from Moscow, he’s from St. Petersburg.'
    answers:
      - is
      - isn’t
      - aren’t
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'Sorry, you $ in room 6, you’re in room 8.'
    answers:
      - aren’t
      - are
      - 'not are'
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'I $ Sara Smith, I’m Sara Simpson.'
    answers:
      - ‘m
      - '‘m not'
      - 'not am'
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'They $ from New York. they’re from Texis.'
    answers:
      - are
      - 'not are'
      - aren’t
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'Jim and I $ from Oxford.'
    answers:
      - is
      - am
      - are
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'Where $ Rosa from?'
    answers:
      - is
      - are
      - am
    correct: 1
